shopwithscrip.com 2015-09-05

# Support

### Legal / 

**Last updated September 15, 2014**

The privacy and security of your confidential information is very important to Great Lakes Scrip Center, LLC (hereinafter referred to as "we," "us," or "GLSC"). This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes what information we collect, how we use that information in providing our products and services to you and how you may opt out of receiving product updates and other information from us. 

When we refer to "Contact Information" we mean your name, address, telephone number, employment status, fax number, and an e-mail address. "Personal Non-Public Information" refers to personally identifiable information about you and transactions in your account, including your social security number, account numbers, any information about your assets, accounts, transaction, and tax status. 

  1. Information We Collect

In order to provide the ShopWithScrip Service to you, we will ask you to provide Contact Information and Personal Non-Public Information. We will collect Personal Non-Public Information about you on applications or other forms, your transactions with us, correspondence between you and GLSC. We collect information about usage of shopwithscrip.com website (the “Web Site”) (for instance, the number of visitors that click on advertisements and links displayed upon our site) and reserve the right in the future to link such usage information to Contact Information or Personal Non-Public Information for each customer or visitor to our Web Site in order to better understand which information or services are of more value to our customers. At times, we conduct online surveys to better understand the needs, profiles, and experiences of our customers and visitors to the Web Site.   Participation in such surveys is strictly voluntary. 

  2. How We Use the Information

We use your information to service your accounts with us, to communicate with you about your accounts, and to obtain your views on the quality of our services. We may also use contact information from time to time to bring to your attention new products and services that we are offering, and to offer to you other promotional opportunities.  You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from us by using the features included in every one of those messages.

  3. Information Sharing

We may share your information in any of the following circumstances:

  1. we have your consent.
  2. we conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preserving or disclosing such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of the Web Site, its users or the public.
  3. the ownership of the Web Site is being transferred and the information is provided in connection with the transfer.
  4. aggregated non-personal information may be shared with third parties, including GLSC retailers.

If you close your account with us, we will retain the information about you and your account in an inactive status. We will not use Contact Information or Personal Non-Public Information about inactive customers for any purpose other than as required in order to carry out our responsibilities with respect to the inactive account. 

  4. Children

The Web Site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and children under such age should not use the Web Site or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.  In the event that we learn that we have collected such information from a child under 13 without parental consent, we will delete the information as soon as reasonably possible.  

  5. Marketing Messages

Granting GLSC permission to send you promotional and administrative messages is a condition of our Terms of Use, and this permission may not be rescinded, unless the relationship between you and us is terminated.  You may opt out of receiving promotional messages by using the features included in each message.

  6. Cookies

"Cookies" are elements of data that a website can send to your browser and store on your computer. Our cookies do not collect or contain personal information about you or compromise the confidentiality of your personal information. Our system automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our site and about the links you may select from within our site to other areas of the Internet or elsewhere online. We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our sites. This way we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites. We reserve the right in the future to link such usage information to Contact Information or Personal Non-Public Information in order to securely verify your identity, to personalize the aspects of your experience on the Web Site and to better understand which information or services are of greater value to our customers. 

We may share aggregated statistical information with our partners, suppliers, and other third parties, but we will not share any personal navigation or other personal information, without your permission. 

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel GIFS or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. You can also erase cookies already stored on your computer. If you choose not to accept these cookies or if you erase them, your experience at our site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. For more information on working with cookies, you should consult the user manual or help function of your specific browser and operating system software. 

While you are browsing the Web Site, you might be directed to websites operated by third parties. These other websites may send their own cookies to you and collect data or solicit personal information. We do not control and are not responsible for what third parties do on their separate websites or how they handle information about you. 

  7. Links

The Web Site may contain links to other web sites that we do not own or control.  WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE PRIVACY POLICIES AND/OR PRACTICES OF THESE LINKED SITES. 

  8. Maintenance of Accurate Information

We strive to ensure that the personal information we have maintained about you is accurate, current, and complete. We will respond to your request to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner. If you find that your personal account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, you should update your account profile by clicking on that link on the Web Site, or if appropriate, contacting us via e-mail. 

  9. Security

GLSC takes the security of information very seriously and has established security standards and procedures to prevent unauthorized access to customer information. We use industry standard means such as physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards, including data encryption and secure socket layer technology. We update and test our technology regularly to maintain and improve the protection of our customers' information. We restrict access to personal information to employees and service providers for legitimate business purposes to assist in providing services to you. Employees who violate our privacy policy are subject to disciplinary action. While we employ appropriate measures to protect against unauthorized access to data maintained by the Web Site, no data can be guaranteed to be completely secure.  WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM RESPONSIBILITY FOR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.    

  10. Last Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 12, 2009.

  11. Web Site Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Web Site, or your dealings with the Web Site, you can contact: webmaster@glscrip.com.
